{
    "subject": "resource/Phillip_Goodhand-Tait",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Kingston_upon_Hull",
    "human_readable": "Phillip Goodhand-Tait was born in Kingston upon Hull.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8971610069274902,
            "question": "Where was Phillip Goodhand-Tait born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7635958790779114,
            "question": "Were there any famous people born in Kingston upon Hull?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6436409950256348,
            "question": "What is Phillip Goodhand-Tait known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5272631645202637,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Phillip Goodhand-Tait's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5078107714653015,
            "question": "Can you provide any sources of information about Phillip Goodhand-Tait?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4218348562717438,
            "question": "What city is Kingston upon Hull located in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4200681447982788,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Phillip Goodhand-Tait's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3996032774448395,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Phillip Goodhand-Tait's work or career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37303245067596436,
            "question": "What are some interesting facts about Kingston upon Hull?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.358929842710495,
            "question": "Does Phillip Goodhand-Tait have any notable accomplishments?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Phillip Goodhand-Tait was born in Kingston upon Hull.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4208_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some interesting facts about Kingston upon Hull?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4208_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Phillip Goodhand-Tait's work or career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4208_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Phillip Goodhand-Tait's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4208_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4208_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4208_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4208_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4208_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4208_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4208_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4208_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4208_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4208_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4208_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that according to document file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4208/re-ranker-msmarco/40.txt, Phillip Goodhand-Tait was indeed born on January 3, 1945, in Kingston upon Hull."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents state that Phillip Goodhand-Tait was born in Hull, East Riding of Yorkshire, England, not Kingston upon Hull."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context clearly states that Phillip Goodhand-Tait was born in Hull, East Riding of Yorkshire, England, not Kingston upon Hull.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}